

Software Developer

Experienced full-stack developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Html / Css, GraphQL, Javascript(Vue.js, Angular,Ionic, Node Js,) , UI/UX , Networking and Graphics Design. Offering 3+ years of progressive experience, specializing in designing and supporting high-volume, high-visibility production and development of applications

EDUCATION'

Bells University of Technology

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Computer Engineering 2013-2018

Topfaith International Secondary School Wassce

2007-2013

Gods Grace International School First school leaving certificate St.

2000-2007

CERTIFICATION'

Google Digital Skills for Africa Digital Marketing Certification

Udacity

Front-End Web Developer Nanodegree(in-view)

Udemy

The Complete Node.js Developer Course (3rd Edition)

Udemy
The Complete Javascript Developer Course

PERSONAL DETAILS

Email: timbetekanem@yahoo.com

Phone No: +2348163056737

Portfolio: https://timbet-portfolio.herokuapp.com

Github: https://github.com/teembet

LANGUAGES

English

INTERESTS

Technical Writing

▶ Traveling

Web Surfing

Sports

Software Developer

WORK EXPERIENCE

ITEX Integrated Services

UI/UX & Front-end Developer

- ~ 01/2020 Ongoing + Victoria Island, Lagos, Nigeria
- Built Responsive web Applications using Angular
- Built User Interfaces for Banks and other financial Institutions using adobe Xd and figma.
- Participated in the building of Interfaces for POS terminals and Reporting Pages
- Worked on the popular Afrimart Project by building the UI for the E- commerce web page

Lagos Reproductive Healthcare Centre

IT Support and Social Media

Marketing(NYSC)

- ~ 01/2019 11/2019 + Lekki, Lagos, Nigeria
- Participated in the Andela Certification for Android, collaborated with other teams to build scalable Apps .
- Gained proficient experience in using Adobe Xd to build user friendly and interactive app templates .
- Used vue js coupled with express framework and hosted with cosmic js to build a portfolio app
- Responsible for maintaining the companies websites and blog in incorporated scheduling and booking appointments.
- Created and handled the companies social media pages to enhance advertisement

<u>Teledom International Limited – Opebi, Ikeja,</u>

Lagos State. Industrial Attachment | April

2017 to September 2017

UI/UX &Software Development

Software Development company

- Completed Development of about 4 websites using WordPress.
- Gained proficient experience in building web apps solutions with Node js and Express framework.
- Built android applications for personal use using android studio and knowledge of java
- Handled repairs and maintenance of desktops and laptops
- Gained knowledge of security solutions like access control and bulk scanning.

Software Developer

WORK EXPERIENCE

WEB AND APP

<u>DEVELOPER(INTERN)</u>

The Roothub, Uyo, Akwa Ibom State. Industrial Attachment

July 2015 - September 2015 + Uyo Akwa Ibom, Nigeria

Web and Mobile Development company.

- Conducted training sessions on Html and CSS for beginners
- Graphic Design using Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator
- Redesigned and maintained websites which improved page load
- Built simple web apps using node and express framework

Bells University of Technology, Ota, Ogun State. Student

Work Experience Program (SWEP) | July 2014 – August 2014

- Operated basic networking equipment devices and tools.
- Coupled and Decoupled computer systems.
- Carried out Computer repairs and maintenance
- Carried out fabrication of various simple mechanical and electronic parts
- Used C++ to write basic programs for projects



Software Developer

INDUSTRY KNOWLEDGE'

Web Development Systems Troubleshooting & Repair Networking Graphics Design

Application Development UI / UX Technical Writing Digital Marketing

Product Design

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Html / Css Vue Js Nodejs MongoDB

MySQL REST API Ionic Angular Typescript

TOOLS AND TECHNOLOGIES

Adobe Illustrator Vuetify Heroku Adobe Photoshop

Adobe After Effect Github Bootstrap Adobe XD

Figma Firebase



Software Developer

PROJECTS WORKED ON

PORTFOLIO APP

Vue,Bulma

• Created a single page Vue-based portfolio website for personal use with bulma as the css framework. https://timbet-portfolio.herokuapp.com

CLICK TO OPEN

COURSESGRAM

Vue, Firebase

Coursegram is an online Web Application connecting users to limitless projects

CLICK TO OPEN

ARISS

Vue, Firebase

• Ariss is online food ordering web application, connecting people with the best restaurants around them.

CLICK TO OPEN

UBA AGENCY BANKING UI

Adobe XD

• A simple ui for uba agency banking team with screens for making transfers withdrawals and vas transactions

CLICK TO OPEN